

Daniel Dominguez

Project Manager /
Certified ScrumMaster®

September 26, 1982 Colombian, Single

K 49 No 91-86 AP 402 Bogotá, CO

> (+57) 319 219 4399 (+57 1) 675 1189

> > dominguezdaniel @live.com

linkedin.com/in/dominguezdaniel

@dominguezdaniel

x.co/idaniel

SUMMARY

Engineer with studies from Colombia, France and Canada. Over 8 years of experience working on Internet-related products and services companies in Colombia and USA. With major expertise on Agile Methodologies, Project Management, Product Development, Digital Marketing and Entrepreneurship.

EXPERIENCE

Product Manager, Webpy webpy.co

Colombia/USA — Jan 2017 - August 2017

Product planning, ideation and release under design thinking and lean methodologies.

Scrum Master, Torre Technologies torre.co

Colombia/USA — Dec 2014 - Dec 2016

Certified ScrumMaster®. Agile scrum development framework for managing product.

Project Manager, DLD Agencia Digital dld.com.co

Colombia/USA — Apr 2014 - Nov 2014

Planning and execution on Google engagement and web app implementations.

Project Manager, VML vml.com

Colombia/USA — Oct 2013 - Mar 2013

Planning, execution and closing projects for Boehringer Ingelheim, Merck and MediaFiche.

Online Marketing Manager, .CO Internet go.co

Colombia/USA — Aug 2012 - May 2013

Tracking and evaluation of marketing initiatives for .CO domains.

Co-Founder, I-Azul i-azul.com

Colombia/USA — Jan 2009 - Jul 2012

Consulting, strategy and development in E-Business, E-Commerce and E-Marketing.

EDUCATION

University of Alberta (Canada)

Specialization, Software Product Management — 2015-2016

Université Pierre et Marie Curie (France)

Master's Degree, Engineering Science — 2008-2008

Université des Sciences et Technologies de Lille (France)

Professional Master, Automation — 2006-2007

Universidad Militar Nueva Granada (Colombia)

Engineer, Mechatronics — 2000-2005

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native), English (Full Proficiency), French (Full Proficiency)

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, GIT, Scrum, Project Management, Online Marketing, Entrepreneurship.

INTERESTS

Robots, Arduino, Programming, Open Source, Reading, Traveling, Formula 1, Zen.

REFERENCES

Omar Duque, Director of Engineering at Huge (+57 300 386 7557) Lorena Dominguez, Sister, Commercial Coordinator at Gluky (+57 320 346 9155)